https://www.youngcuts.com/static/privacy_policy

Account Login
Friday, December 11, 2020
Watch FilmsWatch FilmsWatch Films By YearWatch Films By GenreAbout UsContact UsPrivacy Policy
Helping talented filmmakers build audiences around the world since 2001
Learn More
Privacy Policy
YoungCuts Inc. (“YoungCuts”) is committed to maintaining the confidence and trust of our visitors. To this end, we maintain the following privacy policy to protect the personal information you provide online.  By using YoungCuts’ youngcuts.com web site, you agree to be bound by this privacy policy.
Information Gathering, Usage and Privacy
When you register at the YoungCuts.com web site we ask for information such as your name and email address.
We also collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer including survey and site registration information.
YoungCuts uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.
The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you have requested, when we have your permission, or if  it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
We will never ask for personal information directly from children under the age of 16.
Although YoungCuts owns the data storage, databases and all rights to the videos and other content at its websites, you retain all rights to your data and we will never sell or share your client data with any third-parties. We respect the privacy of our subscribers, and the privacy of their data.
Security
The YoungCuts.com website and service has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as perfect security on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to insure the safety of your information.
Cancellation and Termination
You are solely responsible for properly cancelling your account. You can cancel your account at any time in the Account Manager by selecting "Cancel My Account".  An email or phone request to cancel your account is not considered cancellation.
All of your Content and personal information will be immediately deleted from the Service upon cancellation.
Cookies
A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are required to use the YoungCuts service.
We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies. You are required to log-in to your YoungCuts.com account after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.
Changes to Privacy Policy
YoungCuts may periodically update this policy.  Amendments to this statement will be posted to this URL and will be effective when posted. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification, or change shall constitute your acceptance of the amendment.
We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our site or by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your youngcuts.com primary account holder account.
Questions & Contact
Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to admin@youngcuts.com
ABOUT USContact UsPrivacy PolicyFESTIVALS 2012-15YoungCuts Film Festival 2015YoungCuts Film Festival 2014YoungCuts Film Festival 2013YoungCuts Film Festival 2012FESTIVALS 2005-2011YoungCuts Film Festival 2011YoungCuts Film Festival 2010YoungCuts Film Festival 2009YoungCuts Film Festival 2008YoungCuts Film Festival 2007YoungCuts Film Festival 2006YoungCuts Film Festival 2005
Use of this Web site constitutes acceptance of the YoungCuts.com Terms of Use and incorporated policies.
Copyright © 2020,
YoungCuts Inc. All Rights Reserved.
